Hey guys, I just wanted to tap in. So when you order something from me, you're ordering it directly.
You see how haggard I look right now? That's because I'm putting together orders, right?
I don't have a line at Target or at Kohl's. I am an independent, completely independent creative.
So when you order something from me, I designed it. I sent it to the person who makes it. They sent it back.
Then I got to fulfill the orders, which is put the packaging information as well as the shipping information on the package, the package that I also designed.
Then I got to actually package the items. All right. In the middle of that, I had to pay for the items.
Do you understand what I'm saying? Everything is done by my hand.
And so when y'all send me y'all little emails ahead of the timeframe that I've actually specified, which is like, give me 30 days to do this.
When y'all send me the emails of Karen Indignance, I need to know where my order is.
I just need you to know that you sound a mess.
You're not ordering from Walmart. You're not ordering from a big box company.
You're ordering from an individual. And it is very, it is very conflicting because it's like, are you ordering because you support me or what?
Because you're getting your item and I'm not even past the timeframe with which I have stated that I'm going to get it to you.
But you're talking to me like I done did you dirty for a goddamn t-shirt.
So I just want to remind you that when you are supporting, because we love to say support black folks and we love to say support small businesses and we love to say support women.
And please allow for there to be some more human interactions.
You're not talking to AI. You're not talking to some, you're not even talking to somebody overseas.
You're talking to me. Have some goddamn respect.
You're damn rude.